<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our Team on CAPRO</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/team/</link><description>Recent content in Our Team on CAPRO</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.capro.dev/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Athanasia Mo Mowinckel</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/team/am_mowinckel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/team/am_mowinckel/</guid><description>&lt;p>With a PhD in psychology, Mo transitioned into research software and development as she saw technical solutions could aid fellow scientists in driving their projects forwards.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Emilie Sogn Falch</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/team/es_falch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/team/es_falch/</guid><description>&lt;p>Focusing on data collection, management, and analysis for scientific research, Emilie offers guidance and systematization of data handling and provides data analysis services to support research endeavors.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Inge Kasbohm Amlien</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/team/ik_amlien/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/team/ik_amlien/</guid><description>&lt;p>Tech background and a PhD in psychology /neuroscience.
Inge has a passion for building robust and scalable solutions that allow researchers to focus on their research while maintaining high standards of data security and privacy.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>José-Luis Alatorre-Warren</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/team/jla_warren/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/team/jla_warren/</guid><description>&lt;p>José Luis has a diverse background in engineering (BSc), applied physics (MSc), and evolutionary biology (PhD). He enjoys creating and implementing advanced tools that help make sense of complex pattern in biology and neuroscience.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Maksim Slivka</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/team/m_slivka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/team/m_slivka/</guid><description>&lt;p>With a MSc in Biomedical Engineering with specialization in Computational Neuroscience, Maksim is particularly skilled in processing MR and EEG data. Being on the forefront of technology, he is interested in developing and applying novel solutions to scientific problems.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Markus Handal Sneve</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/team/mh_sneve/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/team/mh_sneve/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dr. Markus is highly skilled, holding a PhD in psychology. He is a dedicated researcher who consistently stays at the forefront of the field through his passion for exploring and discovering new advancements.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>