<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Client testimonials on CAPRO</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/</link><description>Recent content in Client testimonials on CAPRO</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Digital Scholarship Days Workshop</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/dsd_bochynska/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/dsd_bochynska/</guid><description>&lt;p>I attended and co-organized Mo&amp;rsquo;s workshops on data processing, analysis, and reports.
Mo is an excellent instructor who can adapt to different teaching contexts and audiences.
Her enthusiasm for the topics makes the learning experience better.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lifebrain EU-Consortium, University of Barcelona</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lb_dbf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lb_dbf/</guid><description>&lt;p>The University of Barcelona and partners had successful access to the Lifebrain Consortium data thanks to the Capro team’s effective coordination.
Capro organized data in an easy-to-navigate system and provided guidance and updates to ensure high standards.
The data included demographics, cognition, lifestyles, and MRI.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lifebrain, DRCMR</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lb_wb1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lb_wb1/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Capro team has been amazing in creating and maintaining a stable and scalable data management and processing environment.
It has allowed me to successfully process thousands of brain MRI data sets.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lifebrain, DRCMR</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lb_wb2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lb_wb2/</guid><description>&lt;p>The advanced data processing pipelines the LCBC team developed and helped developing, with at times daily online face to face sparring and guidance sessions, have been pivotal to my research.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>R-Ladies website (WordPress to Hugo)</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/rladies_salmon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/rladies_salmon/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed Mo&amp;rsquo;s masterful revamping of the R-Ladies website.
She&amp;rsquo;s put a lot of care in creating a professional and beautiful interface,
but also in creating sustainable update workflows for humans and machines.
Her web development skills increase faster than Hugo version numbers,
she&amp;rsquo;s very resilient to any 502 thrown at her,
and she&amp;rsquo;s a kind and thoughtful collaborator.
200/10 would recommend working with her!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Workshop on data visualisation</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/rladies_meyer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/rladies_meyer/</guid><description>&lt;p>I attended Mo’s workshop on visualization with ggplot2 at R-Ladies Edinburgh in 2021.
Mo is a very competent and enthusiastic teacher who can communicate complex content in an accessible manner. I learned a lot from the workshop and appreciate all the time and effort that went into it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lifebrain, Max Planck Institute</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/mpi_brandmaier/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/mpi_brandmaier/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mo from Capro provided essential support in conducting a mega-analysis with raw data from about half a million people.
She set up and maintained the computing environment on a HPC so that we could run the analysis smoothly and without the data ever leaving the secure storage location.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lifebrain EU-Consortium</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lifebrain_bbf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lifebrain_bbf/</guid><description>&lt;p>The unique and comprehensive Lifebrain database has, thanks to Mo&amp;rsquo;s data management skills, has become a real treasure-trove: she has setup a user-friendly, secure, easy to explore data structure (data from over 5000 participants).
She has additionally organized the Global Brain Health Survey data (over 27 000 respondents) and has made all the data and statistical analyses available for further use.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Center for Lifespan Changes in Brain and Cognition</title><link>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lcbc_kbw/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.capro.dev/testimonial/lcbc_kbw/</guid><description>&lt;p>Capro created a custom database solution for us with our data spanning 15 years of longitudinal data collection.
I am finally able to work with merged and tidy data for my papers, and to explore the entire catalogue of data without assistance!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>